Guide to the Stanford University Postcard Collection
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Postcards (individual)
  - Memorial Church (Exterior), 1904; 1141; Color Print
    Caption: 8578 Memorial Church, Leland Stanford Jr. University
  - Front view of Quad, (from perspective of Chemistry roof ?), 1142; Color print.
    Imprint: R. J. Waters & Co. copyright 1904
    No. 16, Richard Behrendt, Publisher, San Francisco.
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 1143; Color print.
    Caption: Exterior of Memorial Church at Stanford University, California.
    Imprint: Cardinell-Vicent, Co., San Francisco, Oakland, Los Angeles. Made in Germany.
  - Front view of Quad, undated; 1144; B/W Print
    Quad - Front Views - Post 1906; Campus, Aerial Views
  - Old Union, undated; 1145; Color print
    Caption: Union through Arcade Stanford University, California
  - Memorial Church, undated; 1146; Color print
    Caption: Memorial Church Stanford University, California
  - Memorial Church (painting), undated; 1147; Color print
- Mitchell, Edward H. album, pre 1906
- Postcard pack, circa 1950s